{"title": "Toddler Spelling", "listOfQuestions": [{"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "cat", "wrongAnswers": ["kat", "katt", "catt"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "dog", "wrongAnswers": ["dawg", "doog", "dgg"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "apple", "wrongAnswers": ["aple", "appl", "aapl"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "ball", "wrongAnswers": ["balle", "bal", "boll"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "fish", "wrongAnswers": ["fissh", "fich", "fsh"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "hat", "wrongAnswers": ["hatt", "het", "hait"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "car", "wrongAnswers": ["karr", "caar", "kar"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "bird", "wrongAnswers": ["berd", "biird", "baird"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "tree", "wrongAnswers": ["tri", "treee", "tre"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "will", "wrongAnswers": ["wll", "wll", "weel"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "moon", "wrongAnswers": ["mun", "moone", "moom"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "lady", "wrongAnswers": ["laady", "ladde", "ladi"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "milk", "wrongAnswers": ["melk", "mllk", "milc"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "star", "wrongAnswers": ["starr", "staw", "staar"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "chair", "wrongAnswers": ["chare", "chear", "chare"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "box", "wrongAnswers": ["boks", "bax", "boxx"], "timeout": 20}, {"question": "Which of the following spellings is right?", "correctAnswer": "ball", "wrongAnswers": ["baal", "bol", "baall"], "timeout": 20}], "time given": "20"}